Come on tell me Ukrainian Tell me
Давай расскажи мне украинец Расскажи мне
Ukrainian Come on Russian Russian
украинец Давай русский русский
Russian Russian where is Azov
русский русский где Азов
where is good de Good day I ask people from
где добрый де Добрый день Я у людей из
Russia how do you feel about
России спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
the war in
войне в
Ukraine I ask
Украине спрашиваю Тоже
I think the same thing
самое я считаю
and I just talked
и я вот только что разговаривала просто
to the person with the previous one
с человеком с предыдущим
and I  They say Go to the Russians, they
и мне говорят Идите на русские меня
just send me away in plain text. Although I don’t
просто прямым текстом посылают Хотя я не
understand what I personally did and I don’t
понимаю что я лично сделал и я не
understand what I can do in this
понимаю что я могу предпринять в этой
situation. I want this to end as soon as possible. I have
ситуации Я хочу чтобы это поскорее всё
nothing against you personally
закончилось Я ничего против вас лично не
and in general against every single
имею и вообще против каждого отдельно
person.
человек
Look.  I'll try to explain to you why the
смотрите я вам попробую объяснить почему
scientist
уче но
[music]
[музыка]
is
урут сю мто
guilty Please
винова Пожалуйста
explain this state which
объясни это государство которое
is supported by your taxes, that is, you
содержится на ваши налоги то есть вот вы
work, you pay taxes,
работаете вы платите налоги
so Well, yes, I agree, [ __ ]. I personally am an ambassador.
так Ну да я соглас сри Я лично я
Sorry for now,
посло Извини поку
for example, let's say I have nothing to do with
например допустим я никакого отношения к
politics.  I don't have why should I
политике не имею почему я должна
suffer why should I how do you
страдать почему я должна как имеете
have you have look you have a passport of a
имеете смотрите у вас есть паспорт
citizen of the Russian Federation yes yes
гражданина Российской Федерации есть да
a passport of citizenship gives you
паспорт гражданства даёт вам
certain rights and certain
определённые права и определённые
obligations  so that is, there are no rights without
обязательства так то есть нет прав без
obligations So you see, I have
обязательств Так у меня видите прав
no rights If, for example, I write in my
никаких нет Если я например пишу у себя
VKontakte status, they will simply put me in jail, you understand,
ВКонтакте меня просто посадит понимаете
the article is
статья
extremism, you understand, you think We are for
экстремизм понимаете вы думаете Мы за
Putin And if I had children
Путина А если бы у меня были бы дети
For example, I don’t have them, I would  I would agree to
Например у меня их нет я бы согласилась
go to prison so that my children would sit
бы пойти в тюрьму чтобы Мои дети сидели
alone at home with no one knows who Well,
одни дома непонятно с кем Ну а вот
look,
смотрите
let's go Let's go Well, for some reason,
Давай Давайте Так ну вот почему-то мне
many Russians who seem to be against
многие русские которые как вроде против
the war, but they say that if I
войны но они говорят если я там буду
even write there, they'll put me in jail I think
даже писать меня посадят в тр Я думаю
that  some kind of fine, he was drunk but they won't put him in jail
что штраф какой-то выпит но не посадят
because there are
потому есть
people who think he was in jail for extremism, yes And
люди думаете он сидел за экстремизм да А
for
за
what he just published
что просто опубликовал
a show-off What
понтак Это в каком
year was it 2007, oh, not the
году это 2007 ой не
seventh year, and what kind of post was it, what
седьмой го а что за пост был про что там
was it about, and there The thing is that it was against the police
был а там Дело в том что против полиции
if it weren't for our
было если бы не наши
media I would still be sitting
СМИ Я бы сидел до сих
you were convicted or you were simply
пор вас засудили или вас просто
detained and then well there was a trial in prison you
задержали и потом ну суд был в тюрьме
were or
были или
simply served 3 months in
просто 3 месяца отбывал в
prison Wait in prison or there in a pre-trial detention center
тюрьме Подождите в тюрьме или там в СИЗО
as if
как бы
in prison In prison yes that is  you are there
в тюрьме В тюрьме да то есть у вас есть
this sentence is so judicial
этот приговор так судебный
Yes, what city are you from Omsk Russia
Да это с какого города Вы Омск Россия
I understand yes yes Well yes You see yes that is
понял да да Ну да Вот видите да то есть
you can understand Yes, what are you doing
Вас можно понять Да что вы за свою вы
your civic
свою гражданскую
position as if you defined yes that is
позицию как бы определяли да то есть вот
here I can agree that let's say you
тут я могу согласиться что скажем вы
took some actions  -that actions Well,
предпринимали какие-то действия Ну вот
not in relation to this
не относительно кне относительно этой
power there, yes, that is, let's say because
там власти да то есть скажем потому что
I love my power No, I adore my
Я люблю свою власть Нет я обожаю свою
country, but I hate the state
страну но я ненавижу государство Вот
Look, you're an anarchist Yes, he's an anarchist, I
посмотри вы анархист Да он анархист я
guessed, you see Yes, I am No, I'm an anarchist communist,
угадал видите Да я Нет я анарх коммунист
I'm so afraid
я так бо
capitalism Correct Because it is more
капитализм Правильно Потому что при
satisfying to live under capitalism True Of course
капитализме сытнее жить Правда Конечно
if I earn, let's say, 50 a
если Я зарабатываю допустим вот 50 в
month Yes, I am powerful, for example, let's say, yes, I
месяц Да я могучи например допустим да я
bought an apartment, bought a cow and
купила квартиру купила корову и у меня
someone will come and take my cow away from me
придёт кто-то и заберёт мою корову
What Yes, how, how do you get along Here
какого Да а как как как вы уживается Вот
you are  anarcho communist you are a capitalist We have been
вы анархо коммунист вы капиталист Мы
friends for many years it's just that And I
дружим очень много лет просто это А я
thought you were a couple No I understood that Yes yes
думал вы пара Нет это понял Всё да да
because it's in the family It was very hard
потому что это в семье Это очень тяжело
You know if the husband were an anarcho communist
было Знаете так бы муж анархо коммунист
and the wife was a capitalist it would be  it was hard I am
а жена капиталист это тяжело было я я
against communism in general categorically
против коммунизма вообще категорически
we know we constantly argue because of it
мы мы из-за этого постоянно Да ругаемся
Yeah of course it's better But
но мы лучшие друзья Угу конечно лучше А
look if we do
вот смотрите вот если мы всё-таки
return to the topic of war so here uh Russians
вернёмся к теме войны так вот ээ русские
as if say Russians and you too
как бы говорят россияне и вот вы тоже
what if we even write something somewhere there
что да если мы там где-то что-то даже
that they will put us in jail But on the other
напишем что нас посадят Но с другой
hand, in Ukraine I see the city of
стороны вот в Украине я смотрю город
Kherson, so people, the Russians occupied
Херсон так люди э русские оккупировали
it, and people
его так а люди под дула автоматов
come out with Ukrainian flags under the barrels of machine guns, climb out on armored personnel carriers,
выходят с украинскими флагами вылазят на
so it turns out
бтры так то получается
without  courts and investigations And in Russia people are afraid
без суда и следствия А в России люди боя
that they will write something and they
что напишут что-то и за ними
will come for them I in any case I also
придут я в любом случае я вот тоже
constantly talk if with someone That is
разговариваю постоянно если с кем-нибудь
precisely from Ukraine and Damn I still
Вот именно с Украины и Блин я всё равно
can't fully understand this
не могу это понять в полной мере потому
because me  there is no I don't see it I
что меня там нет я этого не вижу я то
mean
есть
and I seriously can't soberly assess the
и я серьёзно не могу трезво оценивать
situation what is happening I am against war in
ситуацию что происходит Я против войны в
any of its
любом её
manifestations Well, what about the information
проявлении Да ну а что с информацие
the city of Mariupol was bombed What other
город там Мариуполь разбомбили Какую ещё
information is there  not presented it right oh
там информацию не так подали
can you Yes yes Let's do it yes we already
ой можно ты Да да Давайте да мы уже так
know it like the media in our ears Well I
это знаешь как нам СМИ в уши Ну я вот с
talked to people who listen to Skabeev
людьми говорил которые скабееву слушают
they have something crazy in their
у них жесть что в
heads we really all have something crazy in our
голове у нас реально у всех тут жесть в
heads everyone is on their ears He's  it
голове все на ушах стоят Он у него
turns out that How many of you had a person
получается Сколько у тебя была человек
working as a courier To at least have something to eat
работает курьером Чтобы хоть что-то есть
he has nothing to eat it turns out 200 rubles an hour
ему нечего есть получается 200 руб в час
he is now paid 120 rubles an hour and the ruble
ему сечас платит 120 руб в час и рубль
has fallen
ещ упал
so now it is not so bad At first
так сечас уже не так всё плохо Сначала
generally
вообще
Uh-huh because they say that there will be more
Угу потому что говорят что ещё будет
sanctions further Yes I don't know will it be worse in
санкции дальше Да я не знаю будет е хуже
general it seems that this is such stupidity
вообще кажется что это такая глупость
In general all this is just incomprehensible for
Вообще всё это просто непонятно ради
what reason that is ra I also don't understand for
чего то есть ра Я тоже не понимаю ради
what reason I don't understand at all for what reason
чего я вообще не понимаю ради чего
negu I will never understand this because
негу я этого никогда не пойму потому что
well I think that it is so  it is impossible this is violence
ну я считаю что так нельзя это насилие
this is violence in any case people suffer
это в любом случае насили люди страдают
Why should people suffer Why do I play
Почему люди должны страдать Почему я вам
with you guys
с ребятами
this is criticism in any case I have
играют это в любом случае в критику Я
already suffered date girl before says
уже пострадал дате девушка до говорит
now Well she says I in any
сейчас Ну она же говорит я в любом
case that is I live in my country Yes
случае то есть я живу в своей стране Да
I am against war but  I live in my country
я против войны но я живу в своей стране
But I still think it's abnormal to
Но я считаю всё равно ненормальным
just attack another country
просто на другую страну
And it's not possible
напасть Да и нельзя
when you remember Donbass and to me
когда вспомните Донбасс и мне
well who is who is broadcasting there Well, let's have
ну кто там кто там вещает А ну давайте
a third one, he is also our friend Oh, I see a friend
третьего это тоже наш друг О я вижу друг
for war Yes,
за войну Да
he is not a little bit for war  but
он немножко не за войну но
he we on orders on orders Yes I'll
он мы по приказу по приказу Да я с
talk to the man Come on come here Dava
человеком поговорю Давай иди сюда Дава
pogo And I'm a military man what about I
пого А я военный человек что по Я тебе
told you come on please please please please
сказал давай пожалуйста пожалуйста вот
Yes we
пожалуйста Да у нас Давайте русский
have Come on Russian came come on
пришёл
tell me Tell me
давайте давай расскажи мне
Ukrainian Come on tell me
Расскажи мне украинец Давай расскажи мне
tell me your flag  hung up Tell me
расскажи флаг свой повесил Расскажи мне
about Donbass Tell me about Donbass
за Донбасс Расскажи мне за Донбасс
Tell tell with Come on calm down
Расскажи рассказывай с Давай успокойся
Come on
Давай
bomb come on just tell me about
бомби давай просто расскажи мне за
Donbass come on don't take her Let me
Донбасс давай не забирайте её Дайте я
talk don't take her Let's watch Come on
поговорю не забирайте Давайте смотрите
tell me
Давай расскажи мне
No not this guy who
Да не вот этот парень который
shouts No you
кричит Нет ты
don't understand where We are from  from
настолько не понимать откуда Мы из
one
одного
city for Donbass you are a rube pa how do you
города за Донбасс ты рубаха па откуда вы
know about
знаете про
Don
Дон
Donbass
Донбас
come on here
давай вот
what happened in Donbass tell me
что случилось на Донбассе Расскажите мне
because we are deceived by our government I
потому что нас обманут наша власть я это
understand this I want to hear your
понимаю я хочу услышать от вас
version well you tell me yourself If you started talking
версию ну ты сам расскажи Если начал
about how funny you are how funny you are
об какой ты смешной какой ты
zas this is in short capital ark
зась это короче капитали арком
russ ti now you are Russian I understand
русс ти вот сейчас Вы русский я понимаю
Russian Russian
русский русский
Russian
русский
Russian where is Azov where A where  you And where is
русский где Азов где А где вы А где
Azov where is Azov Tell the
Азов где Азов Расскажи
wife
жине
AOV which of us is me or you is it
АОВ кто из нас я или ты тебе
funny to you not just I know I have seen a lot of
смешно не просто я знаете я очень много
characters in Cha so but you are simply
персонажей видел в Ча так но вы просто
Unique so far this is the top one for me I am
Уникальны пока это топ один у меня я вот
already giving you a like so look uh you
вам лайк уже ставлю так смотрите ээ вы
see  a very impulsive person and it
вижу очень импульсивный человек причём
is obvious that he is educated because you
видно что образованный потому что ты
woke me up I am educated Yes educated
меня разбудил я образова Да образованный
Yes I can see because immediately
Да вижу потому что сразу
with arguments You say you have higher
аргументированно Говорите д высших
education And what kind of person are you by
образования А какие кто Вы по
profession psychologist engineer
специальности психолог инженер
Oh damn I couldn't hold back Sorry Yes I
Ой блин не сдержался Извините Да я вот
didn't understand after the word psychologist I laughed or
не понял после слова психолог заржал или
after  words
после слова
engineer not nano
инженер не нано
psychologist different from
психолог отличи от
you understand that you have a nervous breakdown
тебя понима что у вас нервный срыв так
because usually when a Russian sees
потому что обычно когда русский видит
Ukrainian Ukrainian la he
украинский украинский ла у него
starts Let's talk about Donbass
начинается Давайте поговорим про Донбасс
after all We are  educated people I
всё-таки Мы ж образованные люди У меня
have two higher educations I am a
есть два высших образования я
programmer and a lawyer and you have two why did
программист и юрист и у вас два что ты
n't you believe me or what? Here we are, I
мне не поверил что ли поверил Вот мы я
say we are on equal terms not like with them
же говорю мы на равных не то что с ними
with these two I spoke like that but like two
с этими двумя так говорил а вот как два
educated people with two  we have
образованных человека с двумя у нас на
four higher educations between us in the army No I
двоих четыре высших образования в арми
haven't I am a citizen you have priority
был Нет не был я граждан у вас приоритет
you see And not everyone is taken into the
видите А у нас не всех берут в
army we are contract
армию нас контрактная
armies let it
армиями пусть
be don't
будет не
buy we don't have Let's talk further
купи у нас нет Давайте поговорим дальше
about
про
Donbass itself
Донбасс сам
SS in the army
СС в армии
wear a
носите
uniform because  I am for Russia not well you
форму потому что я за Россию не ну вы
know that wearing a uniform So if you
знаете что ношение формы Так если вы
were in the army there is a charter of the Armed Forces
были в армии есть устав Вооружённых Сил
wearing a uniform preferable by the way Bro there
ношение формы предпо кстати Братишка
are several whole charters as
есть несколько целых уставов как
if in the Russian army there is a whole one here
бы в российской армии тут целая есть
kakar
какар
all Zami I will tell you now
вся Зами говорить я тебя сечас
and you In which
а вы В каких
troops are you  In what troops did you serve, I am
войсках вы В каких войсках служили там я
a border guard, and where did you guard the border in
пограничник а где границу охраняли на
China? In China, is it because of the Chinese that you
Китае на Китае это вы из-за китайцев
became so nervous? No, I became
такой нервный стали Нет я стал нервный
so nervous because of
такой изза
you. I will
тебя Я к те
come to you in this case,
приду шем случае
VM, but come on,
ВМ но давай
tell me, come on  let's
рассказывай давай давай
bomb Ukraine here Tell me your
бомби на Украину вот Расскажите ваше
opinion
мнение
shut up Come on And
заткни Давай А в
what was it about Yugoslavia when they attacked
чём на югославию когда напали
us
нас
tell me junior
ты сжи мне расскажи мне младшему
sergeant squad leader Tell me about
сержанту командиру отделения Расскажи за
everything why they attacked here explain to me
всё изза чего напали вот объясните мне
why I accepted your Ro I'm telling you again
что я принял вашу Ро Я те ещ раз говорю
Why Yugoslavia  attacked as
За что на югославию напали как
the Yugoslavs said yes Tell me tell me about
югославы да Расскажи мне расскажи мне на
Georgia Come on tell me
Грузию Давай расскажи мне
in m
во м
work Come on tell
работа Давай расскажи
me swineherd And what do you work as Come on I
мне свинопас А кем вы работаете Давай я
don't work as anyone for
никем не работаю
me and what do you earn
мне а чем вы зарабатываете
your living You tell me about history I want to understand
жи Ты мне за истори Я хочу понять
First who am I talking to
Сначала с кем я говорю вот
just  because we say that all
просто потому что у нас говорят что все
Russian soldiers are like that But this is the
русские солдаты они такие А я вот
first time I've seen an educated
впервые увидел образованного солдата
Russian soldier so it's unpleasant
русского так то есть неприятно
to talk to even you at least have a name you
поговорить даже у тебя хотя бы имя есть
have Andrey And you are like Arey Well Andriy it
есть Андрей А вас как Арей Ну Андрий
turns out Andriy so Andriy Vasilevich
получается Андрий так Андрий василевич
yes And what's your name Let's go  tell me
да А Вас как зовут Давай расскажи мне
my name is Alexander your name is Alexander
меня Александр зовут по вашему Олександр
Alexander
Олександр
Alexander Alexander Alexander yes me Sasha  they call you
Олександр Олександр да Меня Саша зовут
yes then it is the same as Pushkin yes they call
да зат это так же как Пушкина да зовут
you who is like
вас кого как
Pushkin I am not Alexander in Pushkin you are the
Пушкина Я в Пушкина не Александр вы так
same as Pushkin Pushkin was also
так же как и Пушкин Пушкин тоже же был
Alexander
Александр
Yes what
Да какой
Pushkin Well there was some kind of
Пушкин Ну был такой какой-то поэт
Russian poet Well yes there was some kind of  Of
русский Ну да какой-то там был у вас же
course not you, yes, they don't teach us anything, we
не конечно да у нас ничего не учат у нас
don't have schools here, we have nothing, how do you
школ здесь нет у нас ничего не чем вы
earn your living?
зарабатываете на жи
I'm Alphonse, that is, in between
я Альфонс то есть в перерывах между
drinking, I just lie down, women. In short, they
пьянкой я просто лежу бабам Короче они
give me money for this. God, who needs you?
мне за это деньги дают Боже а кому вы
Well,  I at least know how you can maybe
та Ну я хотя бы умею умеете может быть
yes well that's it Tell me
да хорошо вот так Расскажите мне
anyway why Russia attacked
всё-таки из-за чего Россия напала на
Ukraine Well come on what a
Украину Ну давай че
good year everything is OK so Avangard shut up
год хорош всё Нор так Авангард помолчи
we are talking to a person right now
мы сейчас вот с человеком говорим
Avangard Be patient come on in short come on I
Авангард Потерпи давай короче давай
remember it was in the year you  you jumped, you
вспоминаю было в году ты скакал ты
jumped,
скакал
here's the score, whoever doesn't jump, whoever doesn't jump, he
вот счет кто не скачет кто не скачет тот
did it like this.
вот так делал
And what else did they shout on the Maidan?
Да а что ещ кричали на Майдане
And what do
а что
you think is correct about what
там правильно по-вашему говорит что что
they shouted on the Maidan?  Come on tell me
кричали на Майдане Давай расскажи мне
come on come on You
давай давай Ты сам себя
buried yourself you buried me right here you
закопал ты меня закопал здесь прям ты ты
woke me up you woke me up
меня разбудил ты меня разбудил
and now you're telling me And what happened on
и ты сейчас мне говоришь А что было на
Maidan in the damn year Come on tell me
Майдане в чертом году Давай расскажи мне
come on tell me come on tell me well
давай рассказывай давай расскажи хорошо
If you want you can listen be silent for a minute
Если хотите вы сможете послушать минутку
so that  don't open your mouth
помолчать чтобы не открывать свой ротик
Okay Okay so look what year
Хорошо Окей значит смотрите в чем году у
we had a president just like you but
нас был президент такой же как вы так но
kind of older
как бы постарше
ideally so he wanted to become
идеально вот и он хотел стать таким как
like Putin so
бы как Путин так
that
чтобы
even ideally ideally no you're holding on you're
даже идеально идеально нет держишься
holding on well done yes Here But we're good
держишься молодец да Вот Но мы хорошо
spicy  the Ukrainians will fall behind we are a
пряня отстанет украинцев мы
freedom-loving nation and we sent him
свободолюбивая нация и мы его послали
where we sent him now a Russian
туда куда послали сейчас русский корабль
military ship so let's go But you Russian
военный так вот давай Но вам русским
Nazis won't understand this you will have it there you
наци это не понять у вас будет там вы вы
will be sitting in Omsk
будете сидеть в Омске
nations nations Yes you know because look
нации нации Да знаешь потому что смотри
you will be sitting in Omsk in  in a crammed
ты будешь сидеть вот в Омске в забитой
apartment, for example, there is no money. So
квартире так например там без денег Так
you will be sad. Your ruler
ты будешь печально у тебя твой правитель
will be chic and you will bow.  him and the
будет шикова и ты будешь кланяться ему а
Ukrainians brother So you know I
украинцы братишка Чтоб ты знал я никому
don't bow to anyone at all I don't bow to anyone you're a child
не кланяюсь вообще я никому не кланяюсь
with your back held high Yes I
дишь с гордо поднятой спиной Да я никому
don't give a damn to anyone you support Putin why do you
не кла ты поддерживаешь Путина чего
support Putin I support yes about the
Путина поддерживаешь я поддерживаю да о
clan he Look he is one of you I see Here are the
клане он Смотри он из вас я вижу Вот
first two interlocutors They at least  understand
первые два собеседника Они хоть понимают
Why Russia lives in poverty because
Почему Россия живёт бедно потому что там
they are robbed from above And you support
сверху их обкрадывают А вы поддерживаете
Putin, so I am for capitalism Come on
Путина поэтому я за капитализм давай
Wait and I Come on Arrestovich - who is
Подожди а я Давай арестович - это кто
Arrestovich
арестович
Vozhi Tell me who is
вожи Раскажи мне кто такой
Arrestovich Arrestovich is a Ukrainian uncle
арестович арестович це украинский дядько
What kind of Russian uncle is
який говорить российскою дядько
Ukrainian Yes Ukrainian uncle We have
украинский Да украинский дядьку У нас у
we once had one like that tell me what's
нас когда-то был такой расскажи мне как
your name Alexander Yes your
тебя Александр Да тебя
[music]
[музыка]
name is Come on Tell me Andrey Who
зовут Давай Расскажи мне Андрей Кто
is Aristovich
такой аристович
Pozha dude of which there are a lot in Ukraine who are
пожа чувак которых в Украине куча от
bombing you Look come on come on let's go
бомбит Вот смотри давай дава давай
back you are bombing Yes you are
всё-таки вернёмся вас бомбит Да вас
bombing Arrestovich Arrestovich  They're bombing us, yes,
бомбит арестович арестович нас бомбит Да
we Russians, and you in front of them  this how to
нас русских А вы перед этим как
talk here I have already 5 days 5 years I
поговорить сюда Я уже 5 дней 5 лет я
see 5 years because I would have 15 years oh
вижу 5 лет потому что я бы же 15 лет та
you can see because two educations
о видно потому что два образования
somehow Gone yes somehow Gone yes yes I and what
как-то Ушло да как-то Ушло да да я и что
Yeah good but you are a psychologist you have
Угу хорошо а вот Вы психолог у вас
first education psychology So
первое образование психология Так дай
no engineering and the second psychology yes Yeah
нет инженерия а вторая психология да Угу
and that is you already the second meaningfully And
а то есть вы уже вторую осмысленно А
can you uh tell me for example uh what are
можете ээ сказать например э какие
the foundations of
основы учения
Jung's teachings He doesn't even know who this Jung is a
Юнга Он даже не знает кто это Юнга
follower of Freud I say girl to
последователь Фрейда Я же говорю девушка
girl respect Everything is okay I'm silent I'm
девушке респект Всё ладно я молчу я
silent  she is there I see the smartest of you
молчу она там Я вижу самая умная из вас
yes the smartest I am more of a military man than a
так да самая умная я больше военный чем
woman and that is for you the cabin boy is the one who
жен а то есть для вас Юнга это который
washes on the ship you know this cabin boy
там моет на корабле вот этого юнгу вы
yes And you don't know that cabin boy but to me
знаете да А того Юнга не знаете а мне
more
больше
Oh well you can really make fun of me  Cabin boy on a
Ох Ну ты прям в юмор можешь Юнга на
ship Are you serious
корабле Ты серьёзно
at all, you are a border guard, you are not
вообще да вы ж пограничник вы не не
a sailor Yes, I understand, I understand So look We are
моряк Да я понял понял Так смотрите Мы
returning to this question, you
возвращаемся к такому вопросу вы
support Putin and therefore, as I
поддерживаете Путина и значит я так
understand it, you support the war against
понимаю вы поддерживаете войну против
Ukraine Putin is our president I am a military man
Украины Путин наш президент Я военный
I don’t care at all  me order Where are you
мне вообще у меня приказ А где вы
military you don't even have a chevron chevron no
военные у вас даже шеврон шеврон нет
order you go to the military registration and enlistment office I'm in this form
приказ вы до военкомата Я в этой форме
the task of driving in general driving or driving How is it
задачу езд вобще ез дю или езжу Как
correct e I don't know how in the language how
правильно е я не знаю как по мове как
in Russian in the
по-русски по по
language Hedgehog Dzhu that's how Hedgehog Dzhu  there is
мове Еж джу вот так ежу Еж Джу таго
no such word we have a slightly
слова нет такого слова у нас мова трошки
better language I would even say Trishki Trishki oh
краща Я бы даже сказал Тришки Тришки о
listen you see You are in Omsk in Omsk but
слухай бачишь Ты в Омске в Омске но
a little educated I see Yes linguist
немножко образованный вижу Да лингвист
Polyglot well look let's still
Полиглот хорошо смотрите давай всё-таки
because of What did Russia from this Omsk
из-за Чего Россия из вот этого там Омска
attack
напала на
Ukraine  izm
Украину изм
these
эти
cities what am
городов что
I I am a cultured person I do not speak
я я культурный человек я не говорю
such swear words
такие
Andre no one attacked Do you know
Андре никто не нападал Ты знаешь вообще
the history of all the events or not I don't know I
историю всех событий или нет не знаю я
ask you to
вот Прошу вас вы меня
enlighten me where they came to you from all
просветили откуда к вам пришли со всех
sides from all regions of Russia ssi from
сторо со всех регионов России сси с
Khakassia from
Хакасии с
Buryat  from Khakassia and Belarus where
буряти с Хакасии а Белоруссия где
Belarus history you don't know and you sit
Белоруси историю не знаешь и сидишь
something to me  you're rubbing it in
что-то мне втираешь
and you're sitting there rubbing it in to me some
анд ты мне сидишь втираешь какую-то
incredible
невероятную
nonsense that you yourself don't
дичь просто за которую сам не
even know about I I I just
шаришь вобще я я я просто сегодня
hit the jackpot today in short
джекпот пиймав короче
pi You're really the jackpot in short ruley
пи Вы реально джекпот короче рулей
jackpot Come on tell me what kind of
джекпот Давай расскажи мне какой ты
catch you have Dude I'm telling you write in short
пойма Чувак я тебе кажу напиши короче
write dude Your father That's it  Don't
напиши чувак Отец твой Всё Не разго
write some card of yours I'll
напиши какую-то свою карточку пару
throw off a couple of rubles later for the fact
рублей скину потом за то
that you
что
take the rubles
руб возми
Well, that's it Glory to Ukraine
Ну всё Слава Украине
Glory to whom Well, you said Glory to
Слава кому Ну вы сказали Слава
Ukraine there's
Украине ть
one thing that made you different from Bandera
одного чем вы отличались от Бандеры
Bandera didn't smoke Bandera wasn't
Бандера не курил Бандера не был таким
like you Bandera was a really
как вы так Бандера был реально
educated person  so I read it and wrote it like
образованным человеком так читал писал
that And you just do it like that Hitler
так А вы только так давай Гитлер тоже
was also an educated person Yes, in principle
был образованным человеком Да в принципе
he was, but he was a tyrant Like your Putin was
был да но был тираном Как ваш Путин был
super
супе
smart even if
умным даже если
damn look there Avangard will break I'll steal
блин смотрите там Авангард поломает
now niches in general he was a
стяну сечас ниши вообще фашист был
specific fascist Well, agree that you are a
конкретный Ну согласись что ты
dialogue definitely I think  viewers will say
диалог однозначно Я думаю зрители скажут
that everything is like  10:0 in your favor, that's for
что всё типа 10:0 в вашу пользу это
sure I just don't understand
однозначно Я вот только не понимаю Вот у
I have one Riddle What is the girl's name the
меня одна Загадка Что как девушку
girl is capitalist What is her name
девушка зовут капиталист Как имя её
Kopeyska I yes Poli What is her name Polina
Копейска я да Поли Как как зовут Полина
Polina here is real respect to Polina here is
Полина вот Полине реальный респект вот
Polina and tell her she is a very smart
Полина так и передайте очень умная
woman the only thing I  not the only one I
женщина единственное я не единственное Я
don't understand what she's doing here among
не понимаю что она делает тут вот среди
you among
вас среди
us I don't understand why
нас Я не понимаю почему
Russians are among you
русские находятся среди вас
honestly Let's finish the dialogue and we
честно Давай закончим диалог и мы
let's we we will take our Donbass and you
давайте мы мы заберём наш Донбасс и ты
will cry on your
будешь плакать на
knees come on laugh I'll see later
коленях давай смейся Я потом посмотрю
how dare you  are your teeth normal
как ты посмеешь у вас зубы нормальные
or not
или нет
something with your jaw there show
что-то с челюстью там Покажите зубы у
your teeth my eye is cut I fought in this in Syria it
меня глаз разрезанный я в этом в Сирии
happened with my eye I am a sniper And what did they
воевал случилось глазом я Снайпер А что
hit you in the eye with a butt No I was hit on the
вам прикладом в глаз ударили Нет мне
highway on the highway And what did you go to
трасе попали трасе А что вы поехали в
Syria I went to Nan
Сирию я поехал Нан
Dale you  you see very well that they gave you a punch in
Дале ты види очень хорошо что вам там в
the eye there you didn't go to Ukraine now
глаз дали Вы теперь на Украину не
well I'll come brother wait for
поехали ну я приеду братишка жди
MASI maximum to the alcohol store you  at
МАСИ максимум до магазина с алко Ты хотя
least take off your warehouse flag
бы свой склад флаг
Look, I'm holding on I hung it up
Сними Смотри я те держусь я его повесил
And you don't even have a flag You
А у тебя даже флага нет Ты даже на шибки
can't even afford shibki You don't have money for a flag I'm
не можешь у тебя денег нет на флаг я
telling you again In this uniform, what do you have
тебе ещ раз говорю В этой форме наба что
on your T-shirt English letters
на майке у тебя английские буквы
What are you  -that
Ты что какой-то
Anglo-Saxon who are you Anglo-Saxon nats
англосакс кто ты англосакс нац
anx What is written on your T-shirt in English
анкс Что у тебя на футболке английские
letters
буквы написано
rollroll So you are anti-Soviet, you are against
ролрол Так ты антисоветчик ты против
Russia You can't even buy
России Ты даже даже не можешь с русскими
yourself a T-shirt with Russian letters te T-
буквами футболку себе
shirt from
футболочку
Come on come on what are you what are you
у Да давай давай что ж ты что ж ты
rock and roll and not Russian  some balalaika
рокенрол а не русскую балалайку какую-то
on Rock'n'roller what Rock'n'roller Russian
на Рокенрольщик что Рокенрольщик русский
Rock'n'roller it's interesting Russian
Рокенрольщик это интересно русский
Rock'n'roller No, that's right rock'n'roll look
Рокенрольщик Да нет так рокен смотрите
rock'n'roll is intellectual music
рок-н-рол - это интеллектуальная музыка
you don't look like a rock'n'roller who are
вы как-то не похожи на рок-н-рольщик кто
you I thought we we we we with you  we talked
вы Я думал мы мы мы мы с тобой общались
normally normally yes and then
нормально нормально да а потом вот
this came I you I will come to you
это пришло Я тебя я приду к тебе
where are you there the [ __ ] in
где ты там находишься наху в
Tomsk in Tomsk So you are in Russia Yes  I'm not
Томске в Томске Так ты в России Да не я
joking in Ukraine Ukraine city
же шучу в Украине Украина город
Khmelnitsky Oh Khmelnitsky woman
Хмельницкий О хмельничанка
tell me Oh yes there are many of yours
ты мне скажи О да там ваших много
who have already died And who is on the kharka Tell me
полегло уже А кто на харке Ты мне скажи
in short let's Give me another shot
короче давайте Дайте мне ещё в кадр
I'll come and say goodbye Yes because
пону тебя приду попрощайся Да потому что
she is an adequate person I want to
она адекватный человек я хочу с ней
say goodbye to her  okay and because I
попрощаться нормально и потому что мне
already have to go Give me Polina in the frame
уже надо будет идти Дайте мне в кадр
for a minute I'll agree with her normally for
Полину на минутку я с ней нормально
a minute so Polina here's
договорюсь минуту так Полина вот вам
real respect to you for your position I
реально респект за вашу позицию меня она
somehow liked her so the only thing I'm
как-то понравилось так единственное Я
saying is that you need to hear You want to
говорю что вам надо слы Ты хочешь
hear That's it  to
слышать Вот и
all
всём
ozheni it is your Of course the choice is so But let's
ожени это ваш Конечно выбор так Но
say I liked your position
скажем вот мне понравилась ваша позиция
so that is you are a very educated prominent
так то есть вы очень образовано видный
person and you understand this but the environment
человек и понимаете этом но окружение
sees us you know as Socrates said
нас видите знаете как говорил Сократ
Tell me who your friend is and I will tell you
Скажи мне кто твой друг и я скажу тебе
who you are
кто ты
with a machine gun SK 47 caliber
с автоматом СК 47 калибр
5  I'll come to you and your
5 я приду те и твой
flag for
флаг за
free I'll
бесплат Я твой ла
take off your flag you'll cry
сниму будешь плакать
look here Polina And you have a bruise here where is
вот смотрите Полина А у вас тут э синяк
that from I can now explain how
это откуда я сейчас могу объяснить как
it happened it's hard to believe
это произошло в это сложно поверить у
he also has a black eye here Oh and I have one
него тоже здесь фингал Ой а у меня вот
here, take my big dog She
здесь вали мою большую собаку Она нас
pulled us and we hit each other like this Gami
Потянула и мы ударились вот так вот Гами
understood everything because I thought it was
всё понял потому что я подумал что это
this
вот этот
wild one until I understood everything like this like this
буйный пока всё понял вот так вот така
uh Russian soul see the truth
ээ Российская душа бачите насправди
Russian
Российска
public  neither adequate nor capitalist
публика ни адекватна нка так капиталист
nor ok so what kind of dude
так и рко нормально так який чувак
anarchist incomprehensible And so in short Russian
анархист непонятный И вот короче руский
comes out on
выходе на
stage immediately here in my here in Russian you know
сцену зразу вот по мо вот руски знаете
now climbed out and here of course Dan content
зараз вылез и вот конечно Дан контенту
Zro
Зро
so Tes of course there are so many of
так Тесь конечно
these spl interesting But it's logical
таких досить спл цикаво Але складно чому
why what really we  When they say
тому що насправди ми Коли вот кажуть
Russian soldiers, they
росийськи Солдаты вони та це вот та
come to our land and in Butch,
приходять на нашу Землю и в Буч були
they were there in Mariupol, there is such a character. And
вони там в мариуполи вот таки персонаж А
what about doctors of sciences,
что там Ясь доктора наук приходять так
or intellectuals, on the violin, Gra, in
чи интелигентни на скрипка Гра о таке
short, there is no place for you. So
короче яке немае себе куда ти Так
come here.  to the contract  go
приходи воно в к воно на контракт иде
there because there you can at least
туда так тому что там мож хоть якогось
make some money and not just drink, so drink and so on and
бабла зрубати а не буха отак и буха И
so on and so forth they get drunk on the occupied
так дальше так набухатся на окупованих
territories and commit atrocities I don't
територия и вчиняють бесчинство я не
know why not, so I don't know the signs of
сумськи не завгодно так не знаю звидки в
them, there's a fig in those two, maybe they hit a dog
них финга в тих двох може справ собачку
like that, one of them  in one so and here
вигу так вдарили один в одного так а вот
such sadness good All in all Glory to Ukraine
така печаль добре Всё всм Слава украини
try and reason with what horde we Mom is
тримайся и розум з якою ордою ми Мамо
right because svit ma
справу тому що свит ма
[music]
[музыка]
demilitarized on my Telegram right
демилитаризованной на мий Telegram прям
now axis VN a
зараз ось ВН а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube is
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy with us through scarg ORV in  your ban and
заня нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и
very many videos do not show people
дуже багато видео не показуе людям
information about ST at times so that we Mali
информа про СТ тому для того щоб ми Мали
operational links PPI right now and while
оперативний звязок ппи прямо зараз а пок
there in  telegra okm video there is also interesting and
там в телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
to timely operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с